I mean, you know, concrete can bridge quite a bit, I mean, if you don't fry it on there, but I think it's sometimes. It looks like it just cracked like it's quite where it was supposed to crack, if it was a fact of it.
Can you look at how to do that here? It's in a more than just this kind of thing.
If we are going to address the intersection, I mean, I'm interested to see what we're going to talk to concrete, what does that mean?
It's an entire brick, I mean, if it's minus 12, 13pb.
Yeah, I just thought we're going to pull it up on the, we did one for the, we tried to get the money from the FEMA, and we put these bridges here.
There's to keep tracks like if you keep track of our designers and then the state and the kind of people is lined up, just so we can all talk on the same.
So this is the brick, I think we're going to have to do another, we're going to go to our own.
So right now we're going to a survey, a vast of the do a survey, see what's in any artifacts, a travel artifacts, or any ancient artifacts, or tulivation.
For the ones who do that we're going to go to.
What the color here is these, this is a hundred-year floodplain, what the banks have said.
I just looked at it just to see how close we were to flooding, but when you turn the contours on, you can tell it's, we're not very far from that floodplain.
So we're probably two, three feet above a floodplain, but when it rains and gets saturated, and the water is flooded up high, the water can't drain it.
So it just stays underneath, and so that's how you can get a lot of water in the backfill and it's saturated.
I'm just starting to drop a couple of, or 16-serer, couple of 16-serer, couple of six things.
I've been ancient before you know how you drop four or five inches, and it could take out this like, I can do it again.
So that's something you can do, so.
Yes, it sounds like it's bad because it's failed, but it's failed and it's settled.
So a lot of it's already happened.
So now that you had it, there's some rubber, we can go ahead and pull it up, and he knows exactly what to do.
You just go in there and compact it, maybe add some more water to try that, make it settle a little bit more, and then build up from there.
And so that's so much happened already, so that's, that's the good news that it happened.
You just want to try to get a little bit more, and then build up from there, and then make sure it's going to make sure it's going to make sure.
It is probably dropped.
I just at least four of this six inches, and where it was, the reason to go.
But six inches is not very much, we've got ten full feet of back to less, or five percent.
And back to less, or, if I can, back to the world, can, back to easily dropped, or five percent.
So that's the thing that everyone does that, was it great?
No, I think the brick band will actually help to, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good.
It's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good, it's a good.
I guess that's right. It looked to me. It was like I pushed it up, but it was actually
I think because the fact is breaking everything. It would have bloated up, but it's got so much space between the breaks. I'm sure
I didn't really know what to do. So there's other areas in that. They're not the way that it falls.
There's several areas in that part of the town where all those objects we observe that you can tell,
I mean, it's the fall of six inches in the middle of one spot there.
There's a lot of stuff. It's just years and years of settlement around here.
Yeah, this fact fell. It gets wet and drops a little bit. Especially when you get asphalt and probably would have seen it as soon as it's started with the brick.
The concrete is forgiving and that's that's it up. It's standing, but you know, it can't stand several inches.
It's acting like a bridge. So it's going to break.
The rubber on that intersection. You said you can fix it because they're fine, right?
Yeah, I mean, I can do some temporary right now, so I don't know what I'm going to do.
It's a card game with a smash ball, right? So I'll make some more of a dome rather than, and then you know,
we're going to be in a d-shirt and then we can put it in a pot.
But we're in a house like on a cold patch.
Some of it will make it wet.
It'll be done.
I think we should be doing that.
If you do get fixed-temperer, you're doing most of the things. If you kept it open, you know, made it great, but still.
It helps just water it in there.
So that might be a approach just now.
Why the rain?
It's ugly, you know.
I might not.
Do you think you want to talk about the sewer at all?
Or what is it?
I don't know what the vision of being bringing a work order,
isn't something hard to do, so we can put our videos in.
You know, a D-R, auto-cat maps to GIS, and I'm sure.
I'm sure.
Well, we get, you know, nothing D-I-S.
We get records.
It's similar to the light of the day.
I just, I got something I'll just show you here real quick.
We're doing this for city of battlefield.
We're about 6,000 people and we're in the process of doing it right now.
So this is the organ partners.
It just tells you where the sewers are.
They wanted to know the directions, so we have arrows to tell them which way to flow.
That helps you kind of with dying those things.
We hit this for the Santa Fe, so you could do this for the stormwater.
Like we're standing here at the sixth and the E and not knowing, you know, where's that?
Where's it?
What water is it collecting?
So if you can look at it, you can help diagnose problems and then also when the city crews are
out there, they can use this instead of a paper bag.
So we're doing this.
This has, they had the elevation, inverts, you know, where the water is, the sewers flow
went into the ground and then I had to do one of these.
This was from, they said, we really get the city of Joplin's information.
It's similar.
They just have different way.
They didn't want the arrows.
And this just shows the rammer, the manhole, what elevation it is, you take the ram minus the
emperor, what it flows, and you can figure out how deep it is.
And then this one, the manhole is important to submit, and then the line is clay, age, and this
is one of which, the city of Springfield, this is a built in bargeye, I guess, because we do a lot
more in harmony.
But it's not letting you click on the data, it's showing the data.
So these are liables, which, eventually I have to think something like this, we get set it up
with a liable in French, probably something that's similar to themselves, because it's a little
bit time consuming and we control the cost.
But the manhole, the numbering, the end works, things like that, these are showing how these
don't show the size because it didn't have to be displayed, but if they did, it would show
it with the size.
So these are just some examples of, and then the life of the city and moanette, they
have information, but this is a popular version, but the public version, they don't want you
to be able to click everything.
So some of this stuff from you, you click on these manholes, they won't let you go to the inspection,
they're not hyperlistened.
But on the city's map that we did for them, they can click and then you can pull up to a more
way to see the photos, but for the public version, they didn't want people to see all
this little thing.
So they just push it.
They can see it as, I don't think there's many people other than no one worth the manholes,
or maybe if you're doing a repair, you know, hey, I need to be able to connect them to the
the city has it here, but usually you tell these aren't that quite that, not everybody wants
to know about it.
And then the other thing, just long long term, one thing, what you put this in a GIS, this
is where you can start doing some programming, like five-year plans, keep in track of all
the TV camera that you have and then also, instead of having paper books, it's right down problems.
You can write it into your GIS, so that you can be able to see that note, you know, you know, people turn over, you've got this and there for every left and his knowledge is going to hopefully be sort of putting some of the knowledge in here and being able to transfer it.
But it's not really doing anything that the computer's doing all this at this point.
We just build it and say, hey, read this field and it needs it and it creates these kind of depth of action.
Yeah, yeah.
For a moment, they have we have done the water, the sewer, the sanitary sewer, and then electric, and so on and also.
And then the streets.
But it didn't get that all at one time.
And usually you start with the one that you want.
So sanitary sewer is the one that you want, and you would start with that.
Build the infrastructure for it.
And then, as you got people, or you got a GIS person, you start building it.
Usually, I need to solve this problem.
Like, for example, see a lot of this is where's everything and how does it flow.
If you knew what the sanitary was or the size, the elevations, you could start diagnosing things, you know,
where problems are at.
Why is this 60 inch down here?
I think so.
Should I also project you know, so we wouldn't know that I did this.
So when I go on, then.
People can happen.
And that I'll just finish here with one like example.
I saw five, I came to Anderson in there in 2008.
The guy that had been here before me was here about 30 years.
And I said, say, man, I need to get your information.
So, this time, the desperation.
I had him.
We did one years of his projects.
He came from the sewer off.
And then, passed forward.
I got my boss who've been there 42 years.
So, every project that we've ever done will be drove a hole in the ground.
I did a lot.
Everyone I could give my hands on is on that.
So, my knowledge.
So, knowledge I had.
The knowledge of Steve Brady had been there 42 years ago.
Knowledge of Z.
I've been there 30 years.
See.
So, when every time we quit on these, we hyperlinked to a report.
And I would say these are probably experts about maybe 50.
For the locations of the waiting for.
And then I know for the location.
Why is it?
Two birds are going down.
Should be a map.
So, I could find the information in the field.
So, it's designed for desktop.
But, but my knowledge is much, much bigger than me.
It's the knowledge of everybody in the company.
So, institutional knowledge that you have.
When you leave, it's gone under.
That could be something with the sewer and the sanitary.
That put that knowledge there.
So, that can be used by everyone.
But it's not that it took, you know, it didn't get done over I did, we did one year and say let's do another year.
And I tried to use people that were poor, you know, we used a reception subject.
You remember a tourist, if you 55 years old, who taught her how to do this, and she put all most of it in there.
And one guy broke his leg.
So I put him up with computers that started putting the information.
We just taught her, like, I've had 13 high school students who were from the end of the semester.
They can't provide sun high school and they work in 50 hours.
They learn through, you know, costs that we can't train and try to help them develop, see if they like to be engineers.
And so they help the students just to take them.
They've got it over time.
But it's something that can be done very well, especially with a lot of people.
Everybody can have that in this receptionist, administrative people, project engineers.
Even in the one you have, you can have it in there.
I want to play some.
But then.
You can't run on your honor.
You can just, hey, if you need to put something in, put something else we have.
So someone else can see it.
I've had information I put in the 14 years ago.
I didn't have a project, but I just said I'd meet right this down.
So I ended up putting in there and a couple of times I pulled up.
I forgot I even wrote the note.
And I said, oh, there's still here and it's contained.
So I knew enough that I said, hey, I think there's something here.
I don't know why I did this, but I remember writing it.
It's just notes.
It's that.
Institutional.
You know what I mean?
I mean, I was wondering, John wrote his arm.
Oh, yeah.
I'm going to get involved and come meet.
Retreat.
Yeah.
I have a chamber a lot.
I said they call it a site.
I didn't know what it was.
We didn't want to be on second place.
I'm going to say, I'm going to say I'm going to first.
I'm going to say, I'm going to start first.
I'm going to start first.
Yeah.
So I was being here.
I was being here.
Yeah.
I found out that the CDL like Robert knows you have to have an extra course.
So it was kind of a promise that maybe I shouldn't have promised.
Yeah.
I'm going to say that.
Well.
And I think the world's been there over 50 years.
Well done.
I think the concrete traits.
I think the middle would have 50 years.
One thing.
So I'm better at it.
Yeah.
I think I think I can remember in the end of the day and then get to the end of the day.
When I go to the end of the day and find out about what I'm going to do.
I don't think there were any 60's left.
I think they would have really learned when this small brain might cross-work.
They would have really learned things.
I'm right, preservation, assessment, grant, contract,
and local empowerment libraries.
I'm from preservation, I don't know,
but I've already been in all these materials.
I'm a resident of Psi, just pay the labor.
And here are artists.
Thank you.
I'm a background user system, library director.
I'm a public library.
This is here, a part of each of our community library.
It's still sent.
So we're here because my own public library
has applied for grant, and has been awarded the grant.
And it's called the Oklahoma Collections,
Assessment Plan Program, Health and Cap.
And it's my Oklahoma Historical Records Advisory Board
through the Oklahoma Department of the Libraries.
So this program is to help our preservation and the access
to our tribal collections that are important
to preserving Oklahoma's history, such as genealogy.
And so we have genealogy section,
and we need assistance for recommendations.
And how to care for it, how to preserve it,
or that personal future.
And as many items as we have,
many are irreplaceable.
And so if something happens, it's gone forever.
So we want to make sure that we do it right,
and we ensure the future of the state is that way.
So she's going to kind of work it down to how she's going to do it with the grant.
Okay, so basically what's going to happen with this grant
in this Oklahoma Historical Advisory Board is paying
for observation consultant to come to our library,
and physically do our collections.
She will then assess what we have,
the conditions that it's put under every day,
and then give us recommendations on how you can preserve
the experience as well as we can.
We can then request $250 after she makes her assessment,
and use it to put towards any of the suggestions she gives us.
It doesn't go to work.
It's not much, but it's something we've been looking at
is a online resource called preserve it.
She's been playing with it in standing in items
because no matter what the items are going to
to create something we have several original maps,
whether they need to know library or for the city,
and you want to be able to preserve those
in one of those ways, it's giving it online,
or giving it a different way to be able to preserve it.
So always it's small step.
And I think that they, as part of this grant,
is that we actually get a consultant that is trained to come in
and see exactly where originology is,
how is your all of that information that's located,
how to file everything.
There's no way that we can preserve it,
but it's really there, it's very underlying.
So we're just recommending and helping back
those people to sign off on the grants.
So the grants for the John Pickdorch, my mother used to be big in the genealogy.
It was a lot.
I would say it would help you, but I like this.
It's not a lot.
It was a lot.
It was a lot to me.
Because of the medications, the kids, the walking around the cemetery.
There was a blast over there.
And that's what they were talking about.
It was a blast.
You know what I was saying?
Are you taking my comments?
I'm taking my comments.
I just need one at the station.
I'll just need one at the station.
May I just need one at the station?
Okay.
Yes.
Right.
Yeah.
I'm just taking my comments.
Okay.
The next slide.
The law to perform a dean, but I'm going to try to talk to the doctor and get
led in for the unknown areas, assessors, and signs, if deceased, after the lock 24,
1 by 26, and lock 137, O.P. in the city of Maine.
So in 2003 or whatever reason, I really don't know what's going on there, but Mr. Cot
Green, the earliest part of the client to the city, and there was an error in the legal
station of this, Mr. Cot, normally the burden of getting to the area, and being disuncursionate
and getting to the, but in this case, we have letters and things that are left in the city
of Maine, and it's clear that the city actually prepared these deems, and the error was
the city's error.
Fast forward to today, the property now belongs to Boydowl, and he's wanting to, the error still
exists.
He's requesting that we face the problem, and we're trying to find Mr. Cotron,
and he has to do, we've got some leads that he might be at a couple of addresses in O.P.
He's in letters that came back.
We have no idea where the gym is, or if it's alive or not.
And so this lawsuit will fix the problem.
I anticipate the court-cost counting the publication.
Because we've done the words that we have to publish it in the newspaper.
I would anticipate you around $300, but just be on the same side.
We've got authorized approved up to $500.
We're all in this role.
Mr. Oval, Mr. Oval.
We'll see you.
Yeah.
That is, guys, here.
Should have really been $448.
At least.
It was needed to the city.
Well, the city turned around and needed it to you.
Do you need to do it?
It was a state.
We've got up to the throne.
They're actually in the process.
We've got possession of it.
There are some other legal issues.
And they're not our responsibility.
They're just...
We're still about to do some things to do.
We've got to do this.
We sold the diet.
I don't know.
Consideration was.
That was in 2005.
And there was a correct legal restriction.
There.
So that if it followed me, when we got it, we didn't get this legal property.
Because it had a wrong legal restriction.
But we sold it to be a property.
It would be intended to sell.
But the technical time didn't help it.
Because of this error in the city.
And then it came in.
It would come back.
So that's the whole point of this.
It's a quiet, high-dwarf suit.
It's not a happy people.
It's just a normal way if we can be our responsibility.
You know, I guess we're going to go in there, but, you know, sure we see it, but some of my
partying with the ones that matter, we're not going to go to the piano, you know, I wouldn't
like to play in a very dark house, but it was a very dark house. So we did two of the
eight years of college time, I'm curious how many hours of college time is. So not to exceed
by our dollar for your rent. I don't know if you didn't want your rent for that things.
All right.
Again, we're going to see.
261, 288,600, 348 costs for the National Commission of 111 in the half of those
that was out these one or seven dials out these,
one, one, one, and dials out these,
11 12 ecentral, 11 18 ecentral,
and three 24 d South West,
a really contract contingent upon its mixture
or required contract document,
and approved two major occupiers design and other street gate.
That's pretty correct.
So this is seven of the houses left around L and O and O,
Two of them are on central right there by the walking park and we're going to be 20-40
southwesters of their bridge.
There is one left off there.
We pulled it from the edge because there's a specific setting on it that we need to
have a different point.
We need to report it to hold that the rest of the property is given that.
We put in a bit of documents that there was not a specialist present because we had to
the person who tested for a specialist in the sample of the site.
What's the address of that?
Two of them are on southeast.
another contractor that he is Arthmo, that was 32,576.
I'm talking about, I'll pay you one five.
Yeah.
But if you don't mind my name, it's both.
But it's like the spot, so I'm assuming that was that.
Oh, on the individual houses?
Yeah.
I'm sorry, yes.
I have a few bids.
Yes.
She's in the 27634's, less, less, less, less, less, less, less, less.
Less, too, one, one.
I'm sorry.
Yeah.
And we'll put it back out to the end.
And then we're helpful to get no more house there.
Don't put too much.
No more house, and that's all on the grid.
Well, there's actually two.
We're still negotiating on one.
We have to see you guys at the purchase again.
We're hopeful to get it.
When you say two, you come back two hours and two or one.
So there's two on one, which the city has purchased.
And there's one more house left on that screen.
23 out of southeast.
That we're still in negotiations with people who own their property.
She can go to school.
She can settle it for the city and this.
Is it a rock out?
No.
It's a white house.
It's got a trailer beside it.
Right now.
It's a older, older, older, older.
Not that we're proving love, but $10 on another screen.
Can they change that promotion?
Can't be because we say we're going to come in.
Because it's our time.
So it should be 27, 6, 4, 7, 6, 7, 6, 7, 6, 7.
Second.
Third.
Thank you, Christy.
I'm going to ask him a little bit.
I appreciate it.
Yes.
that the LFP are an exolution of the coalition's net.
And that's a total agreement of us and I,
for the five, three, two, three, two, three.
So, every year we have two, they bring in this portion
that I would be contacted with Steve,
part that they put in, that we get our rebates back and forth,
for being part of the coalition.
So this is a savings to the city,
and it's actually a savings,
again, this year, from what it was last year.
So, our NFP is our benefit broker.
And they have, they create this coalition,
for the description part of our initial plan.
And this is just an amendment,
they're not better pricing because the coalition is growing,
so I just need to submit,
to be able to sign it so we can say it's an amendment,
the show, the description, it's.
You get my back, you're just saying, my,
no, we get my back, we get back in order to check
from CVS, who is on the prescription part of our insurance plan.
And I send this back a rebate check
by some of the prescriptions that I'm sold,
we get a certain percentage of that amendment back.
But where's that one, Bill?
It goes back into our insurance plan.
What does it mean?
Any harm between five and seven thousand dollars?
It's a big most near term.
Is this seven?
What is five?
Is that nine?
Five?
Five.
Well, we're 22, that's 15, removing parks and recreation
from the Mimea, CVV, and the Nemiya,
as the Mimea, and Mexican and Visitor Bureau,
and a sign of certain additional duties
that are for a minor chapter 12,
by some of this taxation and the sign
is the business regulations, our pool, eight,
and 15, right?
Until that section 12, that's two of three
in the definition provided for conflicting provisions,
fulfilling all conflicting wardensis and establishing
affected dates.
Can you read out a deal?
Yeah.
All right, let's go over here.
All right, for example.
Captain Laugh.
We're going to borrow a note.
And you might have thought that way.
So, you thought about me.
Do you know if I had told you you don't have to read the whole story,
or why do that before and why are you not going to.
So, right now, this is the first part of my business.
for combined this morning.
In the VA, in the past year, you've probably got this point.
They were separate for a long time.
The staff is the manager of our wanting to provide them back up.
So the first step of what we did is this ordinance, which we were hoping to take
to see the best changes in the back to see whatever it is right now, because it's
a terrible question.
Thank you.
That's a huge bunch of that from the end of the time.
But it will be called the CV again.
Right now there are nine members of that award, the state's impact before it was seven members.
We are changing the participation of those, so that once everybody's in the floor,
our attention there to have three year-times on that floor, except for one of the members
is in council member.
That is required under the old ordinance and the current ordinance and the new ordinance.
And that person serves as long as they're wanting to do as long as the commission
of the order council group is long as they're reporting back on this council member.
There can be a second person who is on the floor and they would just think of the position of one of the other
six members.
There are a few other minor changes that are being made.
So we added some warning to the tax for instance to bring in the R&DR, the R&DR is never done
into the tax at this point.
A couple of months.
Parts are not covered.
So in any way, just a few minor changes like that.
The real essence of it is to recreate the CV as the CV, as the CV, as the CV, as the CV.
And in the term that you put it was for the authority.
This needs to be done quickly because of a variety of methods.
We're going to have to be in this case, and we have a very quickly large field
come back with the other ones later on the parts.
You don't need to decide, but there will not be a large board in this case.
Right in addition to that, there will not be a large board,
and we'll just say it's for the two of you to see the manager.
And I think that covers this, and this is for the two of us.
I think the biggest thing was that we were emerged,
because we were going to share the $1.50 fee.
Back when that happened when we were bringing on these kind of the recreation coordinator position.
Now that that $1.50 fee has went back 100% to parks,
there really isn't a need to have that combined meeting anymore.
So this just takes us back to be in fully religious tourism of visitor development,
and then letting parks kind of do have their own function.
So the CVB was created by the vote of the people back in 1998 when they passed the hotel motel tax.
It was voted in, so that there would be a convention of visitor's bureau advisory board
that oversaw the administration of that tax and that acted in an advisory role
that would make recommendations to the city council.
So it's really just going back to that original intent without the addition of the parks and wreck as a part of tourism.
And everybody that's on there, everybody that was continued to serve.
The only two people were Joe Morgan and Tara, which I originally had told them they would go back to the parks board,
but I think that's going to be dissolved.
So we'll just have to, can't have that conversation with them,
to just let them know that there wouldn't be a parks board for them to serve on.
So that is the next several items on the agenda.
If you approve this next time, we'll be the emergency cause,
and then 14th or 20 new, the same people that are currently on do the new.
Thank you.
We're getting emergency cause for the 20th or 21st of 2015.
We're going to the 20th or 21st.
I'm putting Mayor's on my action to appoint Governor Dumpel to the Mount of the Missionary
Bureau to serve as chairperson.
Thank you.
Great work.
Good.
Thank you.
You are welcome.
Your Major.
Thank you.
Good morning.
Okay, thank you.
and work in the business from the start of 2015 and part of the business.
What is the difference?
Oh, right.
I think you're in a business.
It's the one you're not on, Brian.
Oh, you're not on.
All the other ones.
You're on.
You're not on that.
Yes.
No.
So you don't ever, they make decisions on their own,
that don't come to the council as to get approved.
You don't have decisions, things.
And there aren't any council members on it.
Brian.
No.
There can't be any council members on it.
All right.
I know.
I asked you separate.
Yeah.
When they need the decision, they're in person.
And we need to go there later, so that's-
The same time, you shouldn't be on the floor.
You're the one who's there.
Yeah.
It's the one who's there.
I'm the one who's there.
I'm not a citizen.
It's the same.
What do you mean?
I mean, this isn't a victims.
This isn't a victim.
It's a victim.
One.
There's a police officer.
I mean, it's not a victim.
No.
I didn't have to talk about it.
So I had the opportunity to help serve
Sir, I want you to talk a little bit.
So we can choose, you know, this post.
There's a lot of good people out there.
And then the question is, some questions.
No, I just want to commend the churches
that got together.
I just happened to find this and got invited
when these people were doing this.
So these several churches that got together,
they're out there every weekend doing this.
So I'm going to, I'm going to, I'm going to just
public collect, commend those people.
I am no way did anything to help.
I just showed up and they're a little bit of food.
They were on Steve at once on Saturday.
I mean, one of the old ghastels,
birbodies, yeah, and all are very, very young.
Yeah, yeah, the problem was there.
He was one of them alive in action.
I tried some of the years that there was three of us
on the other hand.
Anyway, I appreciate people in our communities having that
heart to reach out and help those who are, you know,
you talked to some of these people in the neighborhood.
They were just on the edge and kind of a couple of
that things go the rhythm of that people
and they're just in that place in which one of those
you want to help them to help them to make those
that are serving those ways that they don't have to.
I'm going to say that the veterans pray, the Elx Laude
that lives in the American community, going together,
and did the veterans pray into the free goal.
Last minute, be it.
I'm going to show you how I went from my veterans
to the city of Virginia.
It was a cool deal to see our veterans ever.
Excited to be able to do something to celebrate,
to be celebrated, and be celebrated.
And they celebrated a couple of Jason Moore, who was one of them,
that killed that shit number, and I racked.
And the bridge went over, the Elx Laude,
so we brought a river, his name, for him.
His family was in it.
So it's a good time to recognize those who are
armed to me and be the given off.
And the family, they were happy that they were still remembered
that they weren't forgotten.
One of the guys, my dad's therapist, his name,
I should have been a little bit sure about them.
My dad's daughter was there, and he had passed away quite a while ago.
He was out of decorate and board board two, I believe.
So we had to be more committed to that.
I didn't know about that was not a lot of decorated,
but I knew so a position to take some more of that.
Yeah, and his mom was there.
His mom was going to the police.
So it was good to see those guys get out and do that,
so I'll ready to do them.
My Christian's break him up.
So that's the same with our street lighting,
because we'll be on December the 2nd, but not the 4th.
We've done it.
My other break last year, when our people say that they didn't get to participate,
because they're wound up to a break.
So.
We're going to try to about before this year and see if that really makes them show up wrong.
But anyway hopefully they're not too bad at the beginning bit of effort.
We can see this club with the extra lining at 6 to 30.
Hopefully we don't have the 6 to 20.
We have the 259 KW.
And the 209 KW.
The 259 KW.
We're trying to get apologies there to some of these about a size while we were doing this, so.
That's no fun.
How to talk with.
So hopefully a bit of a bit of a bit of a report.
How to screw the tree all in that way.
Very good.
What's the trace of the year?
Wednesday.
I think something is there.
What's the number of the year next to you that the tree next to the tree?
I think.
I think you'll drive it in.
You want?
Yeah.
You're going to get volunteered.
I just have to do your job at the end.
Sure.
All right.
Anything else?
We're going to, we're going to, we're going to, we're going to, we're going to, we're going to.